Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-233-83), 362854 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-77-84), 362853 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Pan American World Airways / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-46-84), 362852 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Pan American World Airways (Proffer I), 362851 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Pan American World Airways (Proffer II), 362850 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Pan American World Airways (Proffer III), 362849 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Pan American World Airways (Gn IV), 362848 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Pan American World Airways, 362847 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Piedmont / Association of Flight Attendants (3/18/05), 362846 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Republic Airlines / Air Line Pilot Association (RC-MEC-85-9), 362845 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Republic Airlines / Air Line Pilot Association (PHX-83-1), 362844 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Spirit Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants-CWA (39-99-02-10-03; Sick/ Late Policy), 362843 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Irwin S. Astor), 362842 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (George Kanakis Dunn Case), 362841 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Discharge), 362840 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (R.B. Rhodes-Duty time limits), 362839 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Summary Ruling), 362838 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- PAN AM / Flight Engineers International Association (Air Vietnam), 362837 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (Nadale / Halkides), 362836 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-80-83-SFO), 362835 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-80-174-JFK), 362834 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- PAN AM / Independent Union of Flight Attendants (FS-81-76-JFK), 362833 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Tower Air / Association of Flight Attendants (Wenger), 362832 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Four Hour Rule), 362831 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (NY-59-86; Barter), 362830 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Anderson), 362829 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Brown), 362828 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (A-Plan), 362827 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Jakab), 362826 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Meland / Weitzel), 362825 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Pay Date; TWA 22-89), 362824 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- TWA / Air Line Pilots Association (Carl Straub), 362823 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Dent; 85-678), 362822 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Fekete; 83-869 & 82-878), 362821 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Fekete II; 87-154), 362820 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (LaPollo), 362819 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (84-0241), 362818 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (84-0241 remedy), 362817 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Pluister), 362816 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (86-182; Rose), 362815 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- TWA / Independent Federation of Flight Attendants (Yanusz; 87-014), 362814 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Alicea), 362813 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Culberson), 362812 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Dunlap/ Lancioni), 362811 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Grecia), 362810 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Madison), 362809 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Malatesta), 362808 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Vigilante-JFK), 362807 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- TWA / International Association of Machinists (Williams TW-JFK-11-8), 362806 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- TWA / Ozark Airlines (Baldwin), 362805 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- TWA / Ozark Airlines (1988 Ozark Captain Protective Cell), 362804 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (6-92; Air Wisconsin), 362803 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Air Wisconsin, Remedy), 362802 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (DEN 31-99; Kinlaw-Wells), 362801 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 1-03), 362800 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 9-96), 362799 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 13-95), 362798 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 13-04; Pension Contribution), 362797 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (DEN 29-98; Meade), 362796 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Montano, SFT 119-01), 362795 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Nigro), 362794 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Second Officers), 362793 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (SFO 29-99; Tamayo), 362792 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (1st Class Travel), 362791 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Denise West), 362790 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (91-15), 362789 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (91-1; Engelman), 362788 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Hong Kong 88-31), 362787 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Lounges Award), 362786 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- United Airlines (Box 10, Folder 18)
- US Air / US Shuttle (Supplemental Award), 362785 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- USA / USS Award, 362784 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- US Airways Merger, 362783 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- NBA (Birdsong and Edwards), 362782 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- NBA (Birdsong II), 362781 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- NBA (Dwight Davis), 362780 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NBA (Dorsey v. Rockets), 362779 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- NBA (Alex English), 362778 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- NBA (George Johnson), 362777 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- NBA (Gus Johnson), 362776 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- NBA (J. Jones), 362775 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- NBA (King), 362774 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- NBA (Greg Lee), 362773 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- NBA (Bob Love), 362772 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- NBA (Lewis), 362771 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- NBA (Olive v. San Diego), 362770 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- NBA ( John Shumate), 362769 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- NBA (I. Stallworth), 362768 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- NBA (Webster Decision), 362767 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- NBA (Gus Williams), 362766 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (General), 362765 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Goal Keepers Uniforms), 362764 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Right of First Refusal 1988), 362763 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (monies), 362762 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Kunavac), 362761 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Uremovich), 362760 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Paul Wright), 362759 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Chicago Sting (Spalding), 362758 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Cleveland Crunch (Bernard James), 362757 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland / St Louis and Tacoma), 362756 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland), 362755 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland Kazemaini), 362754 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Cleveland (Marinaro), 362753 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Dallas (Ronnberg), 362752 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Furphy / Kansas City Comets), 362751 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- KC Comets / S. Lee, 362750 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- KC Comets / MISLPA (Mitchell), 362749 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- KC Comets / MISLPA (Nanchoff), 362748 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- KC Comets / MISPLA (Wilkey), 362747 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- KC Comets / MISPLA (Parker), 362746 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- MISLPA / Phoenix (Gillett), 362745 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- MISLPA / Phoenix (Stetler / Owcharuk), 362744 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- MISLPA / Phoenix (Albuquerque), 362743 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- MISPLA / San Diego (Ortiz and Cogsville), 362742 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- MISPLA / San Diego (Tabrizi), 362741 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- MISPLA / San Francisco Fog (Rolland), 362740 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- MISPLA / San Francisco Fog (Renery), 362739 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- MISPLA / Tacoma (Ralph Black), 362738 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- MISPLA / Tacoma (Vaccaro), 362737 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- MISPLA / Wichita (Borja), 362736 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- MISPLA / Wichita Wings (Leite), 362735 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Local 1199/ Beckman Downtown Hospital (1330 0372 80), 362734 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Local 1199 / Beth Israel 00539 98), 362733 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Local 1199/ Beth Israel (01326 99), 362732 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Local 1199/ Beth Israel (209 00), 362731 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Local 1199/ Beth Israel (568 91), 362730 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Local 1199/ Beth Israel (1448 98), 362729 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Local 1199 / Beth Israel (97-97; Prunty), 362728 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Local 1199 / Beth Israel (612-95), 362727 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Local 1199 / Brookdale Hospital (949 91), 362726 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Local 1199 / Brookdale (1593 96), 362725 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Local 1199/ Bronx-Lebanon Hospital (1528 85), 362724 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Local 1199 / Hospital for Joint Diseases (Hiring Practices), 362723 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (1693 84), 362722 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (127 97), 362721 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Local 1199 / Jewish Home and Hospital for the Aged (1272 97), 362720 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Local 1199 / Lenox Hill Hospital (842 91), 362719 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Hillside Medical Center (46 84), 362718 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Hospital (369-83), 362717 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Medical Center (2060 96), 362716 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Local 1199 / St. Lukes Roosevelt Hospital (943 96), 362715 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Local 1199 / Lutheran Hospital (626 72), 362714 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Local 1199 / Montefiore Medical Center (1273 92), 362713 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Local 1199 / Mount Sinai Medical Center (1585 92; Sheppard), 362712 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Local 1199 / North General Hospital (302 93; James), 362711 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (1031 99), 362710 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (1228 97; Anyamesem), 362709 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (1173 97), 362708 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (228 97 Prieto), 362707 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (2081 04), 362706 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (1448 96), 362705 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (1325 99), 362704 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (83 99), 362703 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Local 1199/ New York Medical Center (Donald Stoltzfus), 362702 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Local 1199/ United Oddfellow and Rebekah Home (1683 94), 362701 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Local 1199 / St. Lucks Roosevelt Hospital (2 98), 362700 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Local 1199 / Home of the Sages of Israel (1991 98), 362699 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Local 1199 / Southside Hospital (1284-74), 362698 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (Holiday Pay Eligibility), 362697 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (McDonald), 362696 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (Welch), 362695 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Arco (Elmehrath), 362694 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Civil Service Employees Assn. / State of New York (J. Ford), 362693 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Classic Carriers (Liverpool), 362692 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Security Unit Employees Council 82 / State of New York (Drug Abuse Council), 362691 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hygiene; Villegas), 362690 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (G. Farris), 362689 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hygiene Charles Brown Bronx Psychiatric Center), 362688 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Local 102, ILAWU / C.J.Y. Express (Perry), 362687 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Services (Brown), 362686 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Services (Brown), 362685 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Excellent Trucking (Sylvester), 362684 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Excellent Trucking (Martinez), 362683 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Service (Shiel), 362682 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Felson-Feinberg (Severance Pay Claim), 362681 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Guaranty Trucking (Samuels), 362680 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Guaranty Trucking (Samuels), 362679 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Lucky Apparel Carriers (Brown), 362678 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Lucky Apparel Carriers (Charles), 362677 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Local 102, ILAWU / New Deal Delivery Services (Woodley), 362676 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (Barkley; 91-01-1553), 362675 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (90-01-1217), 362674 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Patrolmens Benevolent Association / City of New York (3609-90; Carney and Ramirez), 362673 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Police Benevolent Association / City of New York (A2092 & 93-85), 362672 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Patrolmens Benevolent Association / City of New York (A-2259-85), 362671 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Rutgers Express (Sweatt), 362670 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (Mitchell), 362669 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Sokols Express (Brown), 362668 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Branham and Wilson), 362667 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Bryant), 362666 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Deas), 362665 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Gordon), 362664 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Douglas Hall), 362663 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Onita Johnson), 362662 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Peter Lawson), 362661 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Ronald McClary), 362660 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Juliet Moore), 362659 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Emmanuel Pierre), 362658 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Curtis Sammuels), 362657 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Rivera and Robinson), 362656 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Stead), 362655 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Walker), 362654 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Withers), 362653 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Local 804, IBT / UPS (578-88), 362652 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Local 804, IBT / UPS (Nazario; 188 89), 362651 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Local 804, IBT / UPS (877-88; Shea), 362650 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Local 804, IBT / UPS (8 90), 362649 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Local 177, IBT / UPS (36 93L; dress code), 362648 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Local 804, IBT / UPS (144, 145 & 146 93L), 362647 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Local 102, ILAWU / TSI City Carriers (Newsome, et al), 362646 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Trident Express (Calixte), 362645 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Local 102, ILAWU / Walsh Super Service (Anderson), 362644 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Bridgeport and Port Jefferson Steamboat Company, 362643 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Barge B-80 Arbitration), 362642 (Box 11, Folder 82)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Reinstatement of James T. Kelly), 362641 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Fromm), 362640 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation (Cedric Feuntes), 362639 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation (Probost), 362638 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Turecamo Maritime Agreement, 362637 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation Settlement, 362636 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Morania Oil Tanker Corp Settlement Agreement, 362635 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- Local 333, United Marine Division / Turecamo Maritime, Inc Settlement Agreement, 362634 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- NHL (Belanger / Pittsburgh Penguins), 362633 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NHL / NHLPA (Comparable Exhibit), 362632 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- NHL (Lemieux / New Jersey Devils), 362631 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- NHL / NHLPA (Compliance with Statistical Data Obligations in Salary Arbitration), 362630 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- NHL (Whalers / Oilers), 362629 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- NHL (Whalers / Oilers ), 362628 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- NHL (Iafrate / Bruins), 362627 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- NHL / NHLPA (Joint Exhibit), 362626 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- NHL (Krutov / Vancouver Hockey Club), 362625 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- NHL (Langevin / NY Islanders), 362624 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- NHL / NHLPA (Average League Salary), 362623 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- NHL (Craig / Dallas / Toronto), 362622 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- NHL/ NHLPA (Minimum Compensation Guarantee), 362621 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- NHL (Norwood / New Jersey Devils), 362620 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- NHL / NYLPA (Anderson, et al. Playoff Bonuses), 362619 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- NHL (Pasek / Minnesota North Stars), 362618 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- NHL (Nedved; St. Louis / Vancouver Equalization Payment), 362617 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- NHL / NHLPA (Pro-ration of certain bonuses), 362616 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- NHL (Ramsey / Buffalo and Pittsburgh), 362615 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- NHL (Samuelsson / Pittsburgh Penguins), 362614 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- NHL / NHLPA (Standard Player Contract Issues Penalty Minutes Bonus), 362613 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- NHL (Taglianetti / Pittsburgh Penguins), 362612 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- NHL (Vernon / Detroit Red Wings), 362611 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- NHL (Alexei Yashin), 362610 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- NHL / International Ice Hockey Federation (Yashin), 362609 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- CWA District 13 and Local 13500 / AT&T (Carson), 362608 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- AT&T / IBEW (Crystal Ciccone), 362607 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- AT&T / CWA (Cornell), 362606 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- AT&T / CWA (Hutchinson), 362605 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- AT&T / CWA (Schwarzmeier), 362604 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- AT&T / CWA (Nickles), 362603 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- AT&T / CWA (Neutrality Pittsburgh), 362602 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- AT&T / CWA (Stratigos), 362601 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- AT&T / CWA (Stewart), 362600 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- AT&T / CWA (!-00-185), 362599 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Bell Atlantic / CWA (Halstead), 362598 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Bell Atlantic / CWA (Walton), 362597 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Verizon Connected Solutions (BACCSI) / IBEW, Local 827 (451 99; Emmolo), 362596 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Bell Atlantic / CWA (Ely), 362595 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Bell Atlantic / CWA (CWA 2-96-5 New Job Title), 362594 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of West Virginia / CWA (Morris), 362593 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Lucent Technologies / CWA (Pitts), 362592 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Aluia; 1747-84), 362591 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Bagley), 362590 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Barrett), 362589 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Cookson), 362588 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Hickey); 1383-90), 362587 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Megazzini; 1608 94), 362586 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (McAdoo; 2508-86), 362585 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Minichiello), 362584 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Morris 1837-84), 362583 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (ORourke; 1028-90), 362582 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (1671-77; Transfer of Employees), 362581 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (916-86; Weir), 362580 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- NYNEX Corporation / CWA (1-95-027; A-95-036; Abbott), 362579 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (1-88-198; A-88-126), 362578 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Bruen), 362577 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- NYNEX Mobile Communications Company / CWA (1-91-66; A-91-4 NX), 362576 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (1-83-148; A-83-99), 362575 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Hall), 362574 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- NYNEX / CWA (Holst; 1-93-121; A-93-1TR), 362573 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Pietz), 362572 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- New York Telephone Company / Telephone Traffic Union (Discharge of M. Newham), 362571 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Robinette), 362570 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Tullo), 362569 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (Shift of Tour; A-83-167), 362568 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- New York Telephone Company / CWA (McDuffie; A-87-2739, 362567 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- PA Bell / CWA (0448 89J), 362566 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- PA Bell / CWA (101 95; Shoes), 362565 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- PA Bell / CWA (14 300 2247 84 J), 362564 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- PA Bell / CWA (145 95), 362563 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- PA Bell / CWA (512 99; Dunn), 362562 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- PA Bell / CWA (1568 82J; Dress Code), 362561 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- PA Bell / CWA (14300 1703 85J; Dress Code II), 362560 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- PA Bell / CWA (1772 97; Suspensions and non-payment Sick Leave), 362559 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- PA Bell / CWA (284 98 J; Unilateral Imposition of Alcohol and Controlled Substance Testing Policy), 362558 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- PA Bell / CWA (52 98; Simonovich), 362557 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- PA Bell / CWA (Douglas), 362556 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Verizon / CWA (Wright), 362555 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Verizon / CWA (Michael), 362554 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Verizon / CWA (Howard), 362553 (Box 13, Folder 14)